import React from "react";

const Questions = [
    {
        question: "Who is often referred to as the King of Rock and Roll?",
        answers: ["Elvis Presley", "Michael Jackson", "Freddie Mercury", "Mick Jagger"],
        correctAnswer: "Elvis Presley"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for the hit song Stairway to Heaven?",
        answers: ["Pink Floyd", "The Rolling Stones", "Led Zeppelin", "AC/DC"],
        correctAnswer: "Led Zeppelin"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is considered to be the pioneers of heavy metal music?",
        answers: ["Metallica", "Black Sabbath", "Guns N' Roses", "Van Halen"],
        correctAnswer: "Black Sabbath"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band had a hit song called Sweet Child o' Mine?",
        answers: ["Aerosmith", "Bon Jovi", "Guns N' Roses", "Metallica"],
        correctAnswer: "Guns N' Roses"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the lead vocalist of the band Queen?",
        answers: ["Robert Plant", "Ozzy Osbourne", "Freddie Mercury", "David Bowie"],
        correctAnswer: "Freddie Mercury"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for their album The Dark Side of the Moon?",
        answers: ["The Beatles", "Pink Floyd", "The Doors", "Nirvana"],
        correctAnswer: "Pink Floyd"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the guitarist for the band AC/DC?",
        answers: ["Eddie Van Halen", "Angus Young", "Jimmy Page", "Jimi Hendrix"],
        correctAnswer: "Angus Young"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band's lead singer is Steven Tyler?",
        answers: ["Aerosmith", "Bon Jovi", "Guns N' Roses", "Metallica"],
        correctAnswer: "Aerosmith"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for the song Enter Sandman?",
        answers: ["Metallica", "Guns N' Roses", "Nirvana", "Black Sabbath"],
        correctAnswer: "Metallica"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is often referred to as the Godfather of Grunge?",
        answers: ["Eddie Vedder", "Kurt Cobain", "Neil Young", "Bruce Springsteen"],
        correctAnswer: "Neil Young"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band's lead singer is Bono?",
        answers: ["U2", "The Police", "The Smiths", "The Cure"],
        correctAnswer: "U2"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the lead guitarist for the band Guns N' Roses?",
        answers: ["Slash", "Eddie Van Halen", "Angus Young", "Jimmy Page"],
        correctAnswer: "Slash"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for the album Appetite for Destruction?",
        answers: ["Metallica", "Guns N' Roses", "Nirvana", "Black Sabbath"],
        correctAnswer: "Guns N' Roses"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for the song Smells Like Teen Spirit?",
        answers: ["Metallica", "Guns N' Roses", "Nirvana", "Black Sabbath"],
        correctAnswer: "Nirvana"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the current lead singer of the band AC/DC?",
        answers: ["Brian Johnson", "Bon Scott", "Axl Rose", "Bruce Dickinson"],
        correctAnswer: "Brian Johnson"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for the album Nevermind?",
        answers: ["Metallica", "Guns N' Roses", "Nirvana", "Black Sabbath"],
        correctAnswer: "Nirvana"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the drummer for the band Led Zeppelin?",
        answers: ["Neil Peart", "Phil Collins", "John Bonham", "Dave Grohl"],
        correctAnswer: "John Bonham"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band's lead singer is Mick Jagger?",
        answers: ["The Rolling Stones", "The Beatles", "Pink Floyd", "The Who"],
        correctAnswer: "The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is famous for the song Jump?",
        answers: ["Van Halen", "Bon Jovi", "Guns N' Roses", "Metallica"],
        correctAnswer: "Van Halen"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the lead singer of the band Pearl Jam?",
        answers: ["Eddie Vedder", "Kurt Cobain", "Chris Cornell", "Layne Staley"],
        correctAnswer: "Eddie Vedder"
    }
];

export default Questions;